Hi, my name is Cindy Mastry with Yoga Etc.
Faith is going to help me show the split bow in this clip.
So Faith is going to inhale in and reach her arms up standing in mountain pose.
Good, she's going to extend her left foot forward ground through her left thigh and root down through her left foot.
She's going to engage her core and lift her right leg back and bring her arms all the way down to the floor and extend her leg up to the sky.
So she wants to feel a long line of energy from the crown of her head all the way up to the tip of her toe.
To split the bow she's going to bend her knee and reach back with her opposite hand, reach onto her toe and then lengthen though her thigh, open through her chest and pull her knee upward.
Yes, good job Faith.
Now if you want to take this a little bit further you could also take your hand off the ground and wrap it around your calve and stand in balance.
Beautiful!
In this pose you're surrendering your head to your heart so you allow yourself to lead with your heart.
Beautiful Faith!
That's the split bow, thanks so much.